Yurii Shovkoplias



Personal

Name Yurii Shovkoplias Address 69061 Zaporizhzhia Phone number +380979785764

Email urock190@gmail.com

Date of birth 11-02-1994

LinkedIn https://www.linkedin.com/in/yurii-shovkoplias/



Profile

Former engineer-technologist. I worked at a company that specialized in the manufacture of aircraft engines. Was involved in the development of technological processes for the manufacture and repair of parts and assembly units, the development and maintenance of technical documentation. I would like to change my field of work and receive an offer from an IT company. I am studying at an IT course under the "Java Developer" program and have gained knowledge and practical skills of a large set of Java and Web technologies.



Work experience

Nov 2021 - Present Electrician

Zaporizhzhya Iron Ore Plant, Zaporizhzhya, Ukraine

· assembly, disassembly, repair, testing and maintenance of mechanical and electrical parts of machines, assemblies and mechanisms, signaling and lighting equipment, grounding;

Technology Engineer Aug 2016 - Aug 2021

Motor Sich JSC, Zaporizhzhya, Ukraine

- development of technological processes for the manufacture and repair of parts and assembly units;
- development and maintenance of technical documentation.



E Courses

Java Development course

Oct 2022 - Present

StartUp IT Academy

Java Core, Servlets, JSP, HTML, CSS, Spring Framework, MySQL, Hibernate.



Education and Qualifications

Sep 2015 - May 2016 **Specialist**

Zaporizhzhya National Technical University, Zaporizhzhya, Ukraine

Speciality: Aircraft engine and powerplant production technologies.

Graduated with honours.

Bachelor's degree

Sep 2011 - May 2015

Zaporizhzhya National Technical University, Zaporizhzhya, Ukraine

Field of study: Engines and power plants of aircraft.



Java, Core Java

Spring Framework

Java Server Pages (JSP)

Jakarta Servlet

HTML, Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)

SQL, MySQL

Hibernate

HQL



Interests

Football, Videogames



■ Soft skills

Time management Communication Adaptability Problem - solving Teamwork Leadership Interpersonal skills Work ethic Attention to detail



Languages

Ukrainian

Native

English

В1